Okay, trap stars and trap star rats. This is titled F July 4th because like, really? In 2026, we doing that? Absolutely not. Absolutely not. We're not doing that.
Um, so I am doing an F July 4th sale on my store, Amanda Land Exports. So it's 45%. It's buy one, get one 45% off for all t-shirts. So people missed it when I did it for my birthday. So now I say, you know what, let's just do it again.
Um, four to fourth. So, uh, there's that. That link is right here. Can y'all see the link? Let me know if you can see the link. Someone asked me the other day, actually, I was doing Tavis Smiley's, um, Tavis Smiley's show. And he asked me what I care about the 250th year of the United States. And I was like, so that was my response to that.
Um, yeah. Okay, I'm, I'm pinning the link. So, yeah, we can't, we can't, keep it a buck. Anybody who's on some yay America shit in 2026, you should really be side-eyeing them. And I don't care if they claim, you know, Republican or Democrat or whatever the F, like, that's just silly.
Like, now you, you, you know what this place is. So, like, why would you even still be riding with that? That don't make no damn sense. Hey, Morel. That don't make no sense. Same with the, like, we're not doing, we're not doing fireworks. We all have dogs. The dogs hate it. Okay.
Um, the dogs hate it. And was I talking about the NDIRE thing? What, that NDIRE said to boycott, um, Carisha's song, Spin That? Um, no, I wasn't talking about that.
But I know y'all love to come in here and ask me to speak on, like, hot topics or whatever while recording my live and then take clips and post it on your little toxic platforms.
So, you know, oh, she didn't say to boycott it? Cause that's what I saw in passing. And I just kept on passing because I don't partake in those conversations.
Actually, what I did say was that she also comments in the shade room comments. So, because she was in the shade room comments being shady about me.
So, there's that. Um, nobody is at my door. What, that person is lying. Nobody is at my door.
So, want to let y'all know that I will be doing, um, the Radical Rhythms Experience every second Wednesday in Harlem at the Comedy in Harlem Comedy Club on 147th and St. Nate.
And you can, see, that's it right there. You can go and get your tickets at comedyinharlem.com. And it's a vibe. It's going to be a vibe. If you're not in New York or the tri-state area, you'll be able to join on YouTube Live.
So, yes, Steven Nikoa, you'll be able to join on YouTube Live. And, uh, the cover is $17 with, that's including taxes.
And, um, I don't get, I don't get paid for these shows. So, just so you know, like you support by paying the cover and by donating when you're able to see the live stream for free.
So, support your artists. You need something from me? No. Um, support your artists. Support us. Okay?
So, I came out here to tell you those two things. I got this sale tomorrow, and then we have the show on July 8th.
Does anyone have any questions before I go? Because I do, I was not as productive as I wanted to be. Yes, my aunt.
Any questions? Any questions? Any questions? Any questions? Any questions? Any questions? Any questions before I go?
Oasis of Paint, where are you based? And I can tell you.
When am I coming to the YMCA in Atlanta? I'm not.
No, I did not see Mom Donnie's speech today. Have a wonderful evening, Morrell.
Um, if you are trying to get to the comedy club, you can go on the D train and, hold on, um, you can go on the D train to 145th, but go to the front of the train, and it'll let you out on 47th.
Cabo Verde about to shock the world. Oh, soccer things? What are my thoughts on interracial couples? That's such a, pffft.
I don't really have thoughts on interracial couples. Thank you to Karen Carter, who just placed an order.
Yeah, I don't, I don't really have thoughts on interracial couples.
Unless it's like a situation where it's like, Kamala, and you are married to a Zionist.
You feel me? Like, you're a black woman, and you're married to a Zionist.
And then I'm supposed to believe that you're for black folks? Get the fuck out of here. Like, that's ridiculous.
You saw me having dinner at Mama's Shelter in LA years ago, one night.
Really? I wonder who I was with at Mama's Shelter.
Um, FJ4 coffee mugs? Okay, okay. D train to 45th. I've never done that trip alone.
I mean, it's, where you come, like, tell me where you're coming from, so I can tell you, like, what the easiest way to do this is.
And I still remember the, the New York train system pretty well.
I was telling folks that I'm doing a monthly in Harlem at, uh, Comedy in Harlem every second Wednesday.
And, uh, you can get your tickets, your cover charges at comedyinharlem.com.
Thank you, Mars Welsh, for placing an order. Love it.
We also have a sale going on in my store, amandalandexports.com.
And you can go there and, um, get 45%.
It's buy one, get one 40% off, all tees, um, sweatpants, totes, et cetera.
All right. Don't ask me again if I saw Mom Donnie's speech today.
Please, please. You're coming from New Jersey.
Okay, someone here said, it's a real easy trip and the station is literally, it literally is right there.
Like, you come off the station and you're like, aha, um, oh, that's what's up, Erin Redd.
Thank you for giving us the tea.
You've been getting attacked.
What were you getting attacked for?
I got attacked today for having too much old food in my fridge.
I was attacked.
I was harassed.
Am I in LA at all?
No.
I have no desire to be back in LA.
I'm sorry, Masa, blow on.
Morel, you're funny with the winky winks.
See, if you're missing my lives, my life, I go live on Patreon all the time.
I go live on Patreon all the time.
Did I ever like living in LA?
Of course.
I mean, I was there long enough.
I was, you know, I was there from 2015 to 2024.
So I was there for nine years.
Um, when I first moved to LA, I left New York.
So I really enjoyed being in LA because you had the mountains.
It was like, you had space, you could drive, you know, there was something different.
Um, just energetically, but it was, but then eventually, you know, you start to see what
it really is.
Ms. Seals, can you put the flyer back up so I can take a screenshot?
It's on my, it's actually on the home screen.
On my homepage.
Like it's literally, oh, I need to.
Hold on one second.
Let me do this while I'm paying attention.
Um, I forgot about, I forget about, oh, you forget about Patreon.
Are you happy about the outcome of socialists getting elected in NYC?
We haven't seen socialists get elected in NYC.
They beat their primaries, but they also aren't socialists.
They're democratic socialists.
That is not a socialist.
By literally even in the name, democratic socialists.
Like it's counter, it's, it's an oxymoron.
Like you can't be a Democrat and a socialist.
You're just like, it's just, it's not, that ain't it.
No, I always knew I was on the spectrum.
I just didn't know in what way, but do you understand what I'm saying?
Like democratic socialists, it's not a thing.
I mean, it is a thing clearly, but really there's still Democrats, which is also like,
they're just Democrats that, that, that aren't necessarily bought by corporations yet.
What is, would anyone else say that's fair?
No, I don't sell jewelry, love.
Why is this doing this?
So we agree that's fair?
Okay.
Why am I trying to log in to Linktree so I can add this link and it's just not allowing me to?
Um, how is my mother doing?
I do not know.
I have not spoken to her in months.
Have you ever blocked so many people you got action blocked?
What is action blocked?
Action blocked.
I mean, I have blocked 87 people at one time before.
I had time and I did it.
What is action blocked?
Like basically like Instagram blocks you.
Hey Fatima.
Thank you.
It's CRG.
Okay.
BK Fisherholic.
I define it as an attempt to organize, to operationalize socialism within the current system.
One billion percent.
But I don't know that that's feasible.
And I don't know that that's, why would we want to do that?
Like you can't.
So you're saying they're trying to, the current system cannot operate as a social,
as a socialist system.
And it's literally counterintuitive to it.
So it would crumble.
Cause like socialism undermines a prison industrial complex.
Socialism undermines, um, reproductive.
You know what's, you know what I thought about today?
It's all of this fucking reproductive shit so they can have more babies to traffic.
Is that what that really was about?
Repealing Roe v.
Wade?
One of those things where you're just like, why are y'all going so fucking hard?
Okay.
There's a song that says we are so far past any justice being served within the systems
that exist.
Absolutely.
Is that Rage Against the Machine?
No.
More workers.
Yeah.
So it's July 4th.
Till it's sideways.
Till it's backwards.
Again, there's a sale at AmandaLandExports.com.
Go there.
Get, buy one.
Get $145 off.
All tees, sweats, et cetera.
Um, and you can also come see me in Harlem on July 8th at Comedy in Harlem.
That link is about to be in bio, but they wouldn't let me do it just now.
And, you know, go listen to the album.
So there we have it.
I did what I needed to do.
Everybody have a good one and throw a big fuck you into the sky tomorrow night.
That'll be your fireworks.